groove3.com 2015-06-09

# Groove3.com - Tutorial Videos for Producers, Engineers and Musicians

##  About Us

This is a privacy policy for Groove 3 Inc. Our homepage on the Web is located at [http://www.groove3.com](http://www.groove3.com/). The full text of our privacy policy is available on the Web at <http://www.groove3.com/w3c/policy.html> Users may go to for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information.

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address:

    Groove 3 Inc.
    4412 Spicewood Springs, #104
    Austin, TX  78759
    USA

You may contact us by e-mail at [support@groove3.com](mailto:support@groove3.com). You may call us at 800-460-7509. 

**Basic Elements**

  * **Notice of Data Collected**  
We involuntarily collect, Click-stream data, HTTP protocol elements, Search terms and Cookies, this data is not linked directly to a user or stored with identifying data. We also collect identifying user information required to complete online transactions, all of which is voluntary and soley at the users discretion.
  * **Data Collection Methods**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
  * **Access to Stored User**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: 
    * Change/correct any data we have about you.
    * Have us delete any data we have about you.
    * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
  * **Security of Collected Data**  
Data collected is used only by Groovebox and is stored on secure, dedicated servers.
  * **Redress / Privacy Policy Concerns**  
If you feel that this Privacy Policy is not being met, please contact us at [info@groove3.com](mailto:info@groove3.com). You may call us at 800-460-7509.

**Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals**

We have the following privacy seals and/or dispute resolution mechanisms. If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, they can help you resolve your concern.

  * **Disputes** : We will remedy all disputes through customer service in accordance with the rules of the BBB . Please email disputes to info@groove3.com

**Additional Information**

This policy is valid for 1 day from the time that it is loaded by a client.

**Data Collection**

P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements"). This policy contains 2 data groups. The data practices of each group will be explained separately.

* * *

###  Group "Basic information"

**We collect the following information:**

  * Click-stream data
  * HTTP protocol elements
  * Search terms

**This data will be used for the following purposes:**

  * Completion and support of the current activity.
  * Web site and system administration.
  * Research and development.

**This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.**

**The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:**

> Data collected from all Web users: access logs, and search strings (if entered).

* * *

###  **Group "Cookies"**

We collect the following information:

  * HTTP cookies

This data will be used for the following purposes:

  * Anonymous user analysis.
  * Anonymous user profiling and decision-making.

This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.

The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:

> Cookies are used to track visitors to our site, so we can better understand what portions of our site best serve you.

* * *

**Cookies**  
Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes:

  * Pseudononymous analysis
  * Pseudonym-based decision-making

* * *

**Compact Policy Summary**  
The compact policy which corresponds to this policy is:

        CP="NOI DSP COR CURa ADMa DEVa PSAa PSDa OUR IND UNI COM NAV INT"

The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy.

**Field** |  **Meaning**  
---|---  
`CP=` |  This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.  
`NOI` |  No identifiable information is collected, so no access is possible.  
`DSP` |  The policy contains at least one dispute-resolution mechanism.  
`COR` |  Violations of this policy will be corrected.  
`CURa` |  The data is used for completion of the current activity.  
`ADMa` |  The data is used for site administration.  
`DEVa` |  The data is used for research and development.  
`PSAa` |  The data is used for pseudononymous analysis.  
`PSDa` |  The data is used for pseudononymous decision-making.  
`OUR` |  The data is given to ourselves and our agents.  
`IND` |  The data will be kept indefinitely.  
`UNI` |  Unique identifiers are collected.  
`COM` |  Computer information is collected.  
`NAV` |  Navigation and clickstream data is collected.  
`INT` |  Interactive data is collected.
